<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="movName">
        <item>Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice</item>
        <item>Captain America: Civil War</item>
        <item>X-Men: Apocalypse</item>
        <item>Deadpool</item>
        <item>KungFu Panda </item>
        <item>Finding Dory</item>
        <item>warcraft</item>
        <item>neighbors</item>
        <item>Independence</item>
        <item>The JungleBook</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movPic">
        <item>@drawable/batmansuperman</item>
        <item>@drawable/captain</item>
        <item>@drawable/xmen</item>
        <item>@drawable/deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/kungfupanda</item>
        <item>@drawable/findingdore</item>
        <item>@drawable/warcraft</item>
        <item>@drawable/neighbors</item>
        <item>@drawable/independence</item>
        <item>@drawable/junglebook</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="movDesc">
            <item>As opposed to MCU, DC Entertainment has started its initial phase of comic book adaptations.
    We’ve only seen Superman so far, but that was only the beginning of the story that will unfold starting with “Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice.”
    The ‘Man of Steel’ and the ‘Dark Knight’ are arguably the two most famous heroes DC has ever created.</item>

            <item>The Marvel Cinematic Universe is by far the franchise that made the most progress in the past couple of years.
    Diverse characters in a complex storyline have been firing up the crowd for some time now, which all continues in the form of “Captain America: Civil War.”

            </item>
            <item>
                The “X-Men” is another franchise the MCU managed to successfully transfer from its comic book origins to the big screen.
    With seven movies behind it, “X-Men: Apocalypse” is bound to tell the story of one of Marvel’s greatest villains.
            </item>

            <item>
    2015 was a great year for movie-lovers, especially if you are a fan of comic book adaptations and sci-fi. We’ve seen some great hits this year, including awesome remakes, sequels, and Oscar-worthy features.
    However, 2016 is looking to be just as much fun as this year.
            </item>
            <item>

                The 2008 animated feature “Kung Fu Panda” was a huge hit among kids and adults alike, while its 2011 sequel “Kung Fu Panda 2” only added to the success of the idea and turned one popular movie into a legitimate franchise.
    Now it’s time to revisit Po and his adventures in “Kung Fu Panda 3.”

            </item>
            <item>
                Everyone loved “Finding Nemo” when it came out in 2003. Packed with sea-creatures, humor, and an excellent cast, this animated movie succeeded at entertaining various crowds.
    Now, 13 years later, we finally get to see what happens next.

            </item>

            <item>
                2016 already looks like it’s going to have something for everyone, and this applies to gamers, too.
    Speaking of which, one of the most popular video-game franchises in the world is set to get its very own, live-action movie.

            </item>

            <item>

                When Universal Pictures released the “Neighbors” back in 2014, the audience was able to enjoy a nice mix of Seth Rogen’s pothead humor and Zac Efron’s immature and inappropriate jokes. In 2016, we’ll be able to see “Neighbors 2.”
    The plot of this sequel is currently unknown, as “Neighbors 2” are still in development.

            </item>
            <item>
                There’s no denying that “Independence Day” is one of the most iconic and patriotic movies that ever came out of Hollywood.
For that reason alone, its long-awaited sequel will be welcomed with open arms when it hits the theaters in 2016.

            </item>

            <item>
                By now, we’re all used to seeing comic book adaptations, endless sequels, and recycled classics in the form of remakes.
That’s why we were hyped when we heard “The Jungle Book” is set to be rebooted.
            </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>